





Danny Huang

+61 452504531 | dannyhuang1234@gmail.com | Personal Website: dannyhuangnz.com | NZ Citizen

Professional summary

Full-stack developer currently working as a **Cloud Engineer at National Australia Bank** with a background in **Electrical Engineering specialising in Machine Learning.** Built and deployed **multiple ReactJS web application** from **scratch to production** for NAB bankers utilising AWS services. Heavily involved as a **Quantitative Trader hobbiest** developing **Recurrent Neural Network models** for predictive analysis.

Education

The University of Melbourne

Melbourne, VIC, Australia

M.Eng, Major:Electrical Engineering, specialising in Optimisation and Machine Learning

Jan 2019- December 2020

- WAM:81.6%, First Class Honours
- Thesis: Optimal path-planning/following for Autonomous Vehicles using Partial Environment Information
- Award: 2nd-place People's Choice Award. (/182 Final Year teams)
 - 3rd-place Road to Endeavour Award. (/182 Final Year teams)

B.S, Major: Electrical Engineering

February 2016-December 2018

• WAM:76.1%, Second Class Honours Division A

Exchange Program

Los Angeles, USA

University of California, Los Angeles

September 2017-June 2018

Technical GPA:3.12

Work Experience

National Australia Bank

Associate Cloud (Software) Engineer – Business Lending

01/08/2021 - Present Full-Time

• Junior Cloud (Software) Engineer - Business Lending

11/01/2021-01/08/2021 Full-Time

- Full-stack web application development using Backend For Frontend(BFF) alongside DevOps role and Unit Testing using ReactJS, Typescript, GraphQL,PostgresQL, Jest, Enzyme.
- o Built 2 production ready web applications used by all bank branches in Australia.
- Setup CI/CD Jenkins pipeline infrastructure for app deployment integrating quality checks such as SonarQube, Checkmarx and Deputy.
- o Mentored external contractors (Accenture & DXC) NAB-specific UI development.
- Completed internal 2 week hackathon building app on house price evaluation using Machine Learning (Convolutional Neural Network) based on current housing market features (No.Rooms, carspace, proximity to facilities etc.).
- Full stack developer confident in ReactJS, AWS infrastructure hosting, serverless and scalable solutions (e.g. ECS, DynamoDB, autoscaling etc).

Jacobs Engineering Consultancy

26/11/2019- 21/02/2020 Full-Time

Undergraduate Electrical Engineer (Rolling Stock)

22/02/2020-01/11/2020 Part-Time

- Assisted in a 200k life extension project for V/Line in data analysis for fault finding and providing recommendations to the client.
- Worked on a \$600 billion dollar project for Victorian Government 2050 metro vision procuring rolling stock(trains) in a consortium of 4 engineering consultancies and government agency.
- o Time-managed 4 concurrent projects ensuring deadlines are met.
- Prepared 5 final reports for clients in a span of 3 months.
- Independent on site-visit to client to inspect project progression and updates.

Commonwealth Scientific and Industrial Research Organisation (CSIRO)

19/11/2018-01/03/2019

• Vacation Student Researcher - InterFloat

- Develop & test capacitive sensing method to measure properties of mineral solution within the flotation
- o Use SPICE simulation to develop circuits, Schematic design & PCB layout for test.
- Laboratory based circuit assembly & practical test.

aws certified Machine Learning Specialty





Danny Huang

+61 452504531 | dannyhuang1234@gmail.com | Personal Website: dannyhuangnz.com | NZ Citizen

Project Design

Building a ReactJS App hosting on AWS - Workshop

2021 working at NAB

• Designed and taught a ReactJS workshop to University students teaching them how to create web app and host on AWS using AWS services specifically S3, DynamoDB, Elastic Load Balancer, Elastic Container Service.

Optimal path-planning for autonomous vehicles using partial information

Capstone 2020

- Develop novel advanced control strategies (via machine learning) for autonomous driving (minimise lap time, power consumption, and guarantee collisions avoidance) with partial information of the environment.
- Real-time collision avoidance for static and dynamic obstacles using Mixed-Integer Quadratic Programming.
- Object Identification
- Designed novel optimisation-based controller using SLAM (Simultaneous Localisation and Mapping) that ensures real-time optimal car maneuvering, speed, and safety.

Algorithmic Trading U.S Market Equity Strategy

Year-long Personal Project 2020-2021

 Research/develop/test trading strategies using signal indictor and Neural Network models. Backtesting strategies on BackTrader platform in Python with a sharpe ratio averaging 2.4.

Al Planning for Autonomy

Semester 1 2020

• Developed full autonomous agent with 3 other students for Pac-man game that ensures completion based on time/score/ghost avoidance.

Measuring froth depth in flotation units

Summer Internship 2019

Research Assistant-develop & test capacitive sensing. Schematic design & PCB layout for test. Written Report describing work and outcomes. Verbal presentation describing results and experience.

Exoskeleton Semester 2 2018

Student-based proof of Concept designing light-weight and Inexpensive exoskeleton that assists human body
movement and research into human mechanisms in order to provide assistance efficiently.

Controller for Self-driving Car

Spring Quarter 2018

• Designed a controller that allows a model car to adjust its position relative to its projected position in order to stay in track (lane keeping).

Speech Classification

Fall Quarter 2017

• Designed a deep neural network algorithm that detects, trains, and predicts audio signal speech recognition of male/female voices with **99.4% accuracy**.

Technical Skills

Frontend Tech Stack

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Typescript, ReactJS, React Native, Jest, Enzyme

Backend Tech Stack

 Python, Pandas, NumPy, MatplotLib, Java, C, SQL, MATLAB, TensorFlow, Sagemaker, Keras, DynamoDB, NoSQL, PostgreSQL, EC2, S3, GraphQL, Adobe Analytics, Google Analytics, PEGA CRM,

DevOps Tech Stack

• Jenkins, Docker ,ECS , Kong , Nginx

Hardware

FPGA, PCB Design, Soldering PCB & Dev board, Microchip SAM C MCU, Arduino Uno, Raspberry Pi

Amazon Web Services (AWS) Certification

- Machine Learning Specialty
- Solutions Architect Associate
- Cloud Practitioner

Leadership & Extra-Curricular

Coffee Appreciation for Enthusiasts – Social Media Director

09/2019-Present

 Managing society's social media accounts with weekly posts on events and meetups whilst directing 2 supporting officers.







Danny Huang

+61 452504531 | dannyhuang1234@gmail.com | Personal Website: dannyhuangnz.com | NZ Citizen

References

Satbir Singh Engineer Manager National Australia Bank 700 Bourke St, Melbourne

Work:+61 426219200

Email: Satbir.Singh@nab.com.au

Agustian Agustian

Engineer Manager National Australia Bank 700 Bourke St, Melbourne

Work: +61 423081132

Email: Agustian.Agustian@nab.com.au